JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:30 PM
HAYATO KAWAJIRI
KOSAKU KAWAJIRI
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:48 PM
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
(Listen)
Breakdown, Breakdown
(3, 2, 1) Let's Go!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
Shining Justice begins to sprout
Brand-new bed town
Will we meet? Let's find out
Feeling the sea breeze from the cape
through the tunnel to the tower
We wander into the alley,
drawn to each other
A shadow melts into our hearts
But the golden spirits
shine a light to protect us
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
1999 Bizarre Summer
Our courage keeps the town in bloom
Great Days
JULY 15TH (THURS) 8:50 PM
EPISODE 35
BITES THE DUST, PART 1
JULY 16TH (FRI) 7:30 AM
-MORIOH'S FAMOUS-
MISO-MARINATED COW TONGUE
CRASH
DEADLY QUEEN
KOSAKU KAWAJIRI
JULY 16TH (FRI) 8:24 AM
[WARNING]
DO NOT READ ON.
AN OLD GUY WALKED BY
WITH HIS FLY DOWN.
HE SNEEZED,
THEN EXCLAIMED, "DAMMIT."
A WOMAN CHUCKLED.
IT RAINED.
AT 8:27 AM, LIGHTNING STRUCK
ABOVE THE PEPSI SIGN.
DAD ISN'T REALLY DAD.
HE MADE SOME GUY AND GIRL
BLOW UP WITHOUT A TRACE AT
AN APARTMENT NEAR JOZENJI.
HE'S A BLOOD-THIRSTY MURDERER.
I DISCOVERED HIS TRUE IDENTITY.
HE HAS SUPER-HUMAN POWER.
MY DAD'S NAME IS YOSHIKAGE KIRA
YOSHIKAGE KIRA
THEN ROHAN KISHIBE WAS KILLED.
THE NEW, SUPERPOWERED KIRA
MURDERED HIM.
THEN ROHAN KISHIBE WAS KILLED.
EPISODE 36
BITES THE DUST, PART 2